### Hubungi

anbyaalibia@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anbya-army-ali-018b00163 (LinkedIn)

#### Keahlian Teratas

Front-end Development
Back-End Web Development
Full-Stack Development

Certifications
FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

# anbya army ali

Full Stack Engineer & IT Manager di Jaygee Group

Greater Jakarta Area, Indonesia

# Ringkasan

saya adalah seorang full stack web developer yang tinggal di jakarta indonesia, saya sudah menjalani bidang ini semenjak tahun 2016. dalam membuat web aplikasi saya menggunakan react js,node js, mongodb/mysql.

I am a full stack web developer who lives in Jakarta Indonesia, I have been doing this field since 2016. In making web applications I use react Js, node js, mongodb / mysql.

# Pengalaman

Jaygee Group
Full Stack Engineer & IT Manager
November 2019 - Present
Indonesia

#### **TRANSDEAL**

Chief Technology Officer September 2018 - Present NORTH JAKARTA

I've created and manage the whole system of transdeal business https://transdeal.co.id/

Jay Gee Group Web Software Engineer & SENIOR IT STAFF Oktober 2016 - Oktober 2019 (3 tahun 1 bulan) central jakarta

#### In 2016

- I've created CRM (Customer relationship management) system for All JAY GEE GROUP Business.
- I've created a company website for JAY GEE GROUP Sub-Business (NAHM THAI SUKI AND BBQ).

https://www.nahmthaisukibbq.com/

- help, support and maintenance system for Financial division.

Page 1 of 2

- help, support and maintenance system for Human Resouces division.
- help, support and maintenance system for Operational division.

#### In 2017

- I've created a Human Resources Information system.
- I've created a Human Resouces Payroll system.
- Maintenance CRM (Customer relationship management) system for All JAY GEE GROUP Business.
- Maintenance a company website for JAY GEE GROUP Sub-Business (NAHM THAI SUKI AND BBQ).

https://www.nahmthaisukibbq.com/

#### in 2018

- I've created a POS (point of sales) system for JAY GEE GROUP Sub-Business (NAHM THAI SUKI AND BBQ & ISOIDE JAPANESE RESTAURANT).

#### in 2019

- I maintain all of the systems that I've been created since 2016.

#### **OMEGA SA**

**IT STAFF** 

Juni 2015 - September 2016 (1 tahun 4 bulan)

**CENTRAL JAKARTA** 

maintenance and develop POS (POINT OF SALES) system.

## Pendidikan

bina sarana infotmatika bogor diploma, manajement informatika · (2011 - 2014)